VLADIMIR EVDOKIMOV

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

INFO

job@evladimir.com

(929) 331-7278 · New York

linkedin.com/in/vladimir-evdokimov

SKILLS

Elixir



Phoenix Framework, OTP

JavaScript



ES6, React, Redux, React Native, Ember.js, jQuery

Ruby

0000

Software Design

SQL, Postgres

••••

AWS, Docker

••000

PROFILE

I'm in web development since 2008. Most of my professional career I worked remotely which taught me discipline and gave me the experience to work in distributed teams. I consider my strength to turn ideas into practical software, which involves software design and working with evolving requirements.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer 2014-Present

<u>Tabarnapp</u>; Montreal, Canada (remote)

I developed and maintained multiple client projects, created a mobile app, and built a sales management tool. When the company shifted its focus to the Shopify ecosystem, I developed a Shopify app that helps merchants to import thousands of products from multiple suppliers into a Shopify store.

Lead programmer 2015-2019

<u>GloboMD</u>; New York (remote)

Created a platform that connects patients with doctors worldwide. I've been handling the technical part of the project from an idea to the point when we had an operational business.

Full Stack Developer 2013-2014

 ${\bf robux.kz; Kazakhstan\ (remote)}$

Participated in the development of web-based accounting software for small-to-medium sized businesses. My responsibility was to create and test new functionality working in a distributed team of software engineers and business analysts in a fast-paced startup.

Founder 2010-2012

Rostov Web Design; Russia

Ran my local web development studio that offered corporate website development and search engine optimization.

Programmer 2008-2010

Komtech Plus; Russia

Worked on an internal web-based ERP system being a member of the IT-department in a Russian machine making company.

EDUCATION

Computer Software Engineering 2004-2008

Rostov Electro Technical College, Associate; Rostov-on-Don, Russia